University Art Museum; Records ua601.005
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
1980 December 2-18 Edward Cowley: Recent Works (not in archival holdings)
1981 January 26-February 28 University Student Art Exhibition
1981 January 26-February 28 Mohawk-Hudson Invitational Exhibition: Ethel Magafan and Robert Blood
1981 March 1-April 26 O. Louis Guglielmi Retrospective
1981 March 17-April 16 Photos of Romanesque Mural Paintings (not in archival holdings)
1981 May 10-24 Masters Thesis Exhibition: Barron, Blechman, Carr, Cavalier, Fontaine, Gala, Gallagher, Gerstenberger, Greenberg, Gonzalez, Hass, Johnson, Kreisher, Lineweaver, Long, Maurello, Palmersheim, Scullion, Silverstein, Witzel
1981 June 24-August 1 Brooke Alexander: A Decade of Print Publishing
1981 June 23-July 12 Jeffrey Studenroth: Watercolors (Lobby) (not in archival holdings)
1981 June 30-July 31 Margaret Crawford: Serigraphs and Small Sculpture (not in archival holdings)
1981 September 8-October 7 Nathan Oliveira: Print Retrospedtive 1949-1978
1981 September 8-October 7 Aldo Casanova: Recent Bronzes
1981 October 23-December 18 Yugoslav Drawings: Current Trends
1981 November 5-December 12 Small Sculpture by Vava Stankovic, Marja Vallila, Stephen Day
1982 January 26-February 28 Anand Manu (Bill Wilson): Recent Works
1982 January 26-February 28 Paul Garland: Large Watercolor Abstractions
1982 March 16-April 18 Fabric Into Art
1982 March 16-April 18 The University at Albany Permanent Collection: Selected Works from 1970 to 1980
1982 May 4-23 Masters Thesis Exhibitions: Bartholomay, Bayly, Benenson, Bowen, Brzezowski, Curtin, Fair, Febbo, Gordon, Johnson, Karp, Lohner, Matzke, Mohn, Mooney, Popper, Scharl, Spelich, Simon, Triedman, Wagoner, Weinman (not in archival holdings)
1982 June 24-August 1 1982 Exhibition by Artists of the Mohawk Hudson Region
1982 September 7-October 10 Edward Koren: Prints and Drawings
1982 October 22-November 21 Lotti Jacobi: Thirty Photographs (not in archival holdings)
1982 October 22-November 21 Shamans and Spirits: Myths and Medical Symbolism in Eskimo Art (not in archival holdings)
1982 October 22-November 21 Edward Cowley: Free-Hand Perspective (not in archival holdings)
1982 December 7-19 Fall 1982 SUNYA Student Exhbition (not in archival holdings) Museum
1983 January Movie Memorabilia: From the collection of Arthur Lennig (not in archival holdings)
1983 February 12-March 25 Thom O'Connor: 20 Year Print Retrospective
1983 February 12-20 Albany Impressions (Lobby) (not in archival holdings)
1983 February 23-March 25 Black Women Achievements Against the Odds (not in archival holdings)
1983 April 19-May 22 Masters of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibitions: Bowen, Chapin, Curtin, Fair, Formanek, Frakes, Gordon, Hass, Matzke, Mooney, Mulero, Row, Smith, Wagoner, Weinman (not in archival holdings)University Art
1983 June 28-August 5 Atelier 17: New Directions
1983 June 28-July 10 Masters Thesis Exhibitions: Bari, Andersen, Mary Anderson, Arat, Ashley, Auger, Bonk, Corigliano, Coughtry, DeAndrade, Fitterer, Jaremko, Keane, Lorenz, Lynes, Ressler, Ripps, Scultz, Stinson (not in archival holdings)
1983 July 15-Augut 5 Abstract/Concrete: Clay works by Regis Brodie and Bill Knoble (not in archival holdings)
1983 September 13-October 23 New Decorative Art (not in archival holdings)
1983 September 13-October 23 Artists at Large: Photographs by Rollie McKenna
1983 October 18-December 16 Recent Work by the Univerity Art Faculty
1983 November 1-December 16 Recognitions: Faces and Places / Photographs by Charles Traub
1984 January 24-February 26 Mohawk-Hudson Invitational: Enid Blechman and Allen Grindle (not in archival holdings)
1984 January 24-February 26 Robert Motherwell: Lyric Suite
1984 January 24-February 26 Prints by Fairfield Porter (not in archival holdings)
1984 January 24-February 26 Oshima/MacGregor - Paintings (Lobby)
1984 January 24-February 26 Albany Impressions Suite
1984 March 9-April 13 Rural Vistas: Rediscovery of the American Landscape (not in archival holdings)
1984 March 9-April 13 Twentieth Century American Watercolor (not in archival holdings)
1984 March 9-April 13 Richard Stankiewicz Memorial Exhibition
1984 May 3-20 Master of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibitions: Arat, Anderson, Ashley, DeAndrade, Gala, Giscombe, Jaremko, Leavitt, Lohner, Moninski, Park, Ripps, Rogers, Scharl, Schultz, Spelich, Nancy Engle: Photographs (Lobby) (not in archival holdings)
1984 June 26-August 3 Forever Wild: Photographs from the Adirondacks by Eliot Porter (not in archival holdings)
1984 June 26-August 3 Glory Glory: Photographs by Lionel J. M. Delevingne (not in archival holdings)
1984 June 26-August 3 Freda Hall: Flower Photographs (Lobby) (not in archival holdings)
1984 June 26-August 3 Arbor Hill Children's Art (Lobby) (not in archival holdings)
1984 June 26-July 12 Master of Arts Thesis Exhibitions: Chen, Hollinde, Keays, Lee, Ojalvo, Roberts, Rolando, Testo, Tofield (not in archival holdings)
1984 July 17-August 3 Two Polish Printmakers: Andrzej Kalina and Andrzej Dworokowski (not in archival holdings)
1984 July 17- 24 Two Cool Evenings
1984 September 4-November 14 New York Painters: New Directions (not in archival holdings)
1984 September 4-November 14 The Art of Adornment: Contemporary Wearable Art from Africa and the Diaspora (not in archival holdings)
1984 September 4-November 14 Videotape: Six Works by John Sturgeon (West Gallery) (not in archival holdings)
1984 September 4-November 14 Mural Drawings: Humanities Lounge Project (Lobby) (not in archival holdings)
1984 November 30-December 21 Master of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibitions: Coughtry, Schaming, Stewart (not in archival holdings)
1985 January 22-January 27 The Janus Press 1975-80 - Claire VanVliet
1985 January 22-January 27 Artists' Books: Callner, O'Connor, Schade
1985 February 13-March 17 Eadweard Muybridge: Animal Locomotion
1985 February 13-March 17 New York Printmakers: A Dozen Directions
1985 February 13-March 17 Helmmo Kinderman: Camera Works
1985 April 9-May 19 Master of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibitions: Benenson, Depew, Keane, Klein, Ojalvo, Roberts, Rolando, Testo (not in archival holdings)
1985 April 9-24 Master of Arts Thesis Exhbitions: Chang, Lee, Nutting, Williams (not in archival holdings)University Art May 1-19
1985 April 9-24 Master of Arts Thesis Exhibitions: Webster-Frederick, Reid, Smith (not in archival holdings)
1985 June 25-August 4 1985 Artists of the Mohawk-Hudson Region
1985 September 4-15 Maritime Prints (not in archival holdings)
1985 September 4-October 13 Edward Mayer Sculpture (not in archival holdings)
1985 September 4-October 13 Screenprints by Contemporary Painters (not in archival holdings)
1985 October 25-November 24 David Hockney: Photocollages (not in archival holdings)
1985 October 25-November 24 Photos from the Collection of the University (not in archival holdings)
1985 December 6-20 Master of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibitions: Chen, Egan, Hollinde, Lee,
1985 December 6-20 McCartan, Murphy (not in archival holdings)
1985 December 6-20 Master of Arts Exhibitions: Cheng, Peters, Rochow (not in archival holdings)
1986 February 12-March 23 New York State--An Aerial Perspective: Photographs by Marilyn Bridges
1986 February 12-March 23 Transparencies--Multi-media works by Ten New York Artists
1986 April 14-May 18 Master of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibitions: Avakian, Brandt, Charlton, Englander, Goren, Mohn, Perkins, Warner
1986 April 14-May 18 Master of Arts Exhibitions: Rogula, Simmons, Siren, Sweet (not in archival holdings)
1986 June 24-August 1 A Birthday Party: 50 Years of the Mohawk Hudson Regional
1986 September 2-October 19 The Faces of the City: Albany Portraits from Three Centuries
1986 November 1-26 Olokun Imagery/Objects of Prayer: Cibachrome Photographs by
1986 November 1-26 Phyllis Galembo (not in archival holdings)
1986 November 1-26 Bill Wilson: Return to Landscape
1986 November 1-26 Recent Works by Five Faculty Artists: Ballester, Buchman, Carson,
1986 November 1-26 Plaxco and Vallila (not in archival holdings)
1986 December 9-21 Master of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibitions: Kreishner, Nutting, Vatsky,
1986 December 9-21 Williams Zupnick
1986 December 9-21 Masters of Arts Exhibitions: Ryder, Valenti (not in archival holdings)
1987 January 20-25 Master of Arts Exhibitions: Ryder, Valenti
1987 February 3-March 1 New Drawings - The Drawing Center, NY
1987 February 3-March 1 Elders of the Tribe
1987 March 10-April 10 Beijing/New York: Avant-Garde Chinese Art
1987 March 10-April 10 The New York School: Prints from the University Art Collection (not in archival holdings)
1987 April 21-May 17 Master of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibitions: Chen-yu, DePietro, Peters, Rochow, Stiglich, Wineland (not in archival holdings)
1987 April 21-May 17 Master of Arts Thesis Exhibitions: Clernents, Cuadra, DiGangi, Gray Be, Leff, Liburdi, Papele, Schoonmaker, Trabka, Valentino (not in archival holdings)
1987 June 13-September 6 1987 Mohawk Hudson Regional Exhibition (not in archival holdings)
1987 September 8-October 11 Edward Cowley - A Retrospective (two copies)
1987 September 8-October 11 Donald Mochon Remembered (not in archival holdings)
1987 October 24-November 22 Katherine Porter: Recent Paintings (not in archival holdings)
1987 October 24-November 22 Sandi Fellman: Japanese Tattoo Series (not in archival holdings)
1987 October 24-November 22 Youth Books of Yore: From Pilgrim's Progress to Pinocchio (not in archival holdings)
1987 December 8-23 Master of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibitions: Anderson, Kahn, Shoebridge, Swearingen (not in archival holdings)
1987 December 8-23 Master of Arts Thesis Exhibitions: Brady, Brenner, Miller, Squillace, Wang, Yan
1988 January 20-February 21 Recent Works on Paper by the Fine Arts Faculty (not in archival holdings)
1988 January 20-February 21 The Art Students League: Selections from the Permanent Collection Undergraduate Artists (not in archival holdings)
1988 March 8-April 10 Contemporary Finnish Prints
1988 March 8-April 10 Kosta Bogdonovitch (not in archival holdings)
1988 March 8-April 10 Quilts by Linda O'Connor (not in archival holdings)
1988 April 26-May 15 Master of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibition: Chinian, Huntington, Machell, Ryder (not in archival holdings)
1988 April 26-May 15 Master of Arts Thesis Exhibition: Bocci, Woodbury (not in archival holdings)
1988 June 17-July 24 Artists of the Mohawk-Hudson Region Juried Exhibition
1988 September 6-October 16 The Paintings of Ethel Schwabacher
1988 September 6-October 16 Alumni I
1988 September 6-October 9 Living gods/Hindu Faces (not in archival holdings)
1988 October 25-November 23 Richard Callner: A Retrospective Exhibition
1988 October 25-November 23 Four Centuries of Italian Master Drawings
1988 December 9-December 23 Master of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibition: DiGangi, Papele, Walters (not in archival holdings)
1988 December 9-December 23 Master of Arts Thesis Exhibition: Dermansky, Martin (not in archival holdings)
1989 January 24-March 10 Contemporary American Collage: 1960-1986 (not in archival holdings)
1989 January 24-March 10 Photographs from the University Collection (not in archival holdings)
1989 January 24-March 10 Albany Project: An installation by Susan Rees (not in archival holdings)
1989 March 14-April 16 Seymour Drumlevitch (not in archival holdings)
1989 March 14-April 16 Photographs from the University Collection (cont'd) (not in archival holdings)
1989 May 2-May 21 Master of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibition: Clements, Michael, Squillace, Tabka (not in archival holdings)
1989 May 2-May 21 Master of Arts Thesis Exhibition: Alterman, Bae, Buvoli, Grunwaldt, Harris (not in archival holdings)
1989 June 20-August 1 Reclaiming Paradise: American Women Photograph the Land (not in archival holdings)
1989 September 5-October 15 Sculpture'89: Fellowship Recipients of the New York Foundation
1989 September 5-October 15 for the Arts (not in archival holdings)
1989 September 5-October 15 Olivia Parker: Anima Motrix (not in archival holdings)
1989 October 24-November 19 Zuka: The French Revolution through American Eyes
1989 December 8-December 21 Master of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibition (not in archival holdings)
1989 December 8-December 21 Master of Arts Thesis Exhibition (not in archival holdings)
1990 January 16-February 25 University at Albany Fine Arts Department Faculty Exhibition (not in archival holdings)
1990 March 13-April 12 Aaron Karp (not in archival holdings)
1990 March 13-April 12 The Atelier Project (not in archival holdings)
1990 March 13-April 12 The Albany Impressions Series:Editions made for artists at the print studios of the University (not in archival holdings)
1990 May 1-20 Master of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibitions
1990 May 1-20 Master of Arts Thesis Exhibition
1990 June 26-August 3 Antonio Frasconi: An Artist's Journal
1990 June 26-August 3 Edward Colker
1990 September 5-November l8 Contemporary Art of the African Diaspora (not in archival holdings)
1990 September 5-November l8 New York Foundation for the Arts Fellowship Recipients (not in archival holdings)
1990 September 5-November l8 Portraits of an Epoch: The Drawings of Benedikt F. Dolbin (West Gallery)
1990 December 1-21 Master of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibitions (not in archival holdings)
1990 December 1-21 Master of Arts Thesis Exhibitions (not in archival holdings)
1990 February 2-March 17 Our Land/Ourselves: American Indian Contemporary Artists
1990 April 3-April 21 Robert Arrandale Williams: The American Terrain
1990 April 3-April 21 Rudolph Serra: Sculpture (West Gallery) (not in archival holdings)
1990 May 4-26 Master of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibitions: Krepfle, Lail, Lipman, Schloemer, Valentino, Walters, Wright-Sedam (not in archival holdings)
1990 May 4-26 Master of Arts Thesis Exhibitions: Rock, Ryan, and Setchfield (not in archival holdings)
1990 July 16-September 8 Artists of the Mohawk-Hudson Region Juried Exhibition
1990 October 1-November 24 Art Faculty Exhibition
1990 October 1-November 24 Dorothy Lathrop: A Centenary Celebration (West Gallery)
1990 December 4-22 Master of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibitions: Brenner, Ginett, Jones,
1990 December 4-22 Lewis, McGreevy (not in archival holdings)
1990 December 4-22 Master of Arts Thesis Exhibitions: Flynn, Green (not in archival holdings)
1992 January 15-February 16 Gardens: Real and Imagined
1992 March 3-April 12 Through the Object's Eye: Paintings by Joan Semmel
1992 March 3-April 12 Swiss Poster Art 1906-1990 from the Ciba-Geigy Collection
1992 March 3-April 12 California/Albany (West Gallery)
1992 March 3-April 12 The View From Here: Claremont
1992 May 8-17 Master of Fine Arts Thesis Exhibitions
1992 May 8-17 Master of Arts Thesis Exhibitions
1992 June 23-July 26 Convergence: Eight Black Photographers
1992 September 12-November 24 Living Traditions: Mexican Popular Arts (two copies)
1993 March 2- April 23 Jasper Johns: Prints and Multiples
1994 March 8 - April 17 Dennis Byng, Richard Callner, Edward Cowley: Creating After Teaching: Three Faculty Emeriti (two copies)
1994 June 7 - July 31 Artists of the Mohawk Hudson Region Juried Exhibit
1994 September 24-November 13 Democratic Vistas: 150 Years of American Art from Regional Collections (two copies)
1995 January 17-February 19 Warrington Colescott: A Retrospective Exhibition
1995 March 25-May 21 Geoffrey Holder: Painter
1996 March 12-April 21 Robert Cartmell: Painting, Prints, Drawings, 1971-1996. A Twenty-five Year Retrospective
1996 June 5-July 21 Artists in the Kitchen (two copies)
1996 September 7-November 3 Visions of New York State: The Historical Paintings of L. F. Tantillo (includes a copy of the teachers guide)
1996 September 7-November 3 Witness and Legacy: Contemporary Art About the Holocaust
1997 June 17-July 31 1997 Artists of the Mohawk Hudson Region Juried Exhibit
1997 September 21-November 9 Memory and Morning. Shared Cultural Experience
Scope and Contents
Exhibit Publications contains exhibit leaflets, flyers, catalogs, and programs from 1967 to 1993. All exhibits held by the University Art Gallery and subsequently Art Museum are listed. The items are arranged chronologically by exhibition. The list of exhibits was compiled and annotated by both the Museum and the University Archives to describe holdings relating to the exhibits. While all exhibits held by the University Art Gallery and subsequently Art Museum are listed, full documentation for all the exhibits may not exist. For the most part the University Archives and the University Art Gallery have duplicate holdings. Where an item is not held by the University Archives the note (not in archival holdings) will appear.
Newspaper clippings were gathered by both the University Archives and the Art Gallery and subsequent Museum. For the most part, clippings were gathered from local publications relation to exhibits.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is divided into two series: exhibit publications, and a clippings file.
Art; Art museum architecture; Web Archives; UAlbany Centers & Institutes; Wages -- New York (State); State University of New York at Albany
- Exhibition Publications, 1967-1997; 1
- Clippings, 1965-1992; 2
- Art Museum Website, 1997 June 16 - 2013 June 1; 3; 69 captures
  URL
  http://www.albany.edu/museum
  Access Requirements
  The item contains web archives preserved as WARC files. They must be access though web archival replay tools such as the "Wayback Machine." The links here direct you to files hosted by the Internet Archive, but you may also request WARC files.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service.
  This item is not a seed within an Archive-it collection, but capures of this page are found within:
  collection: University at Albany, SUNY Website
  created_date: 2012-09-17T13:15:00Z
  created_by: bkeough
  state: ACTIVE
  last_updated_date: 2016-09-26T23:38:05Z
  last_updated_by: system
  Web Collection
  - University Art Museum, Albany, NY, 1997 June 16
    This crawl was performed by the Internet Archive, not the UAlbany web archiving program, so the provenance is unknown.
  - University Art Museum, Albany, NY, 1997 July 25
  - University Art Museum, Albany, NY, 1997 October 22
  - University Art Museum, Albany, NY, 1999 January 16
  - University Art Museum, Albany, NY, 1999 February 19
  - University Art Museum, Albany, NY, 2000 February 29
  - University Art Museum, Albany, NY, 2000 August 15
  - Page Not Found -- University at Albany, 2000 October 3
  - University Art Museum, Albany, NY, 2001 January 24
  - Page Not Found -- University at Albany, 2001 April 22
  - not present, 2001 April 24
  - not present, 2001 June 3
  - not present, 2001 June 3
  - University Art Museum, University at Albany, 2001 August 11
  - University Art Museum, University at Albany, 2001 November 9
  - University Art Museum, University at Albany, 2002 August 6
  - University Art Museum, University at Albany, 2002 October 10
  - University Art Museum | University at Albany, 2003 December 4
  - University Art Museum | University at Albany, 2004 October 13
  - University Art Museum | University at Albany, 2005 February 3
  - University Art Museum | University at Albany, 2006 April 2
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2010 May 27
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2010 December 7
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2010 December 8
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2010 December 15
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2011 January 5
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2011 January 12
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2011 February 7
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2011 March 9
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2011 March 23
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2011 April 27
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2011 May 18
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2011 May 25
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2011 June 1
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2011 June 3
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2011 June 8
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2011 June 28
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2011 August 19
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2011 October 12
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2012 January 21
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2012 January 23
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2012 February 10
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2012 May 4
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2012 May 8
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2012 June 11
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2012 June 15
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2012 July 1
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2012 July 4
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2012 July 16
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2012 August 11
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2012 October 12
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2012 October 15
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2012 December 1
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2013 January 2
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2013 January 19
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2013 February 1
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2013 February 22
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2013 February 22
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2013 March 1
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2013 March 24
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2013 April 1
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2013 April 13
  - University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2013 May 1
  - WARC file for University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2013 May 8
    This item had no crawl rules.
    The CDX index for this capture did not contain crawl information.
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Researchers interested in data analysis with web archives may request a WARC file. WARC files are very large and difficult to work with. Your request may take time to process, and we may be unable to deliver your request remotely. Please consult an archivist if you are interested in advanced research with web archives.
  - WARC file for University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2013 May 8
  - WARC file for University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2013 May 15
  - WARC file for University Art Museum - University at Albany - SUNY, 2013 May 22
  - WARC file for not present, 2013 May 29
  - not present, 2013 June 1